sharpbargains.com 2011-10-24

# Custom T-Shirts | Screen Printing | Embroidery| SharpBargains.com

Thank you for accessing the Sharpbargains.com Website (“Site”) operated by Sharp Bargains, LLC. We respect your privacy and want to protect your personal information. To learn more, please read this Privacy Policy below. **  
****  
We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices on any web site not operated by Sharp Bargains, LLC to which the Site links or that links to the Site.  
**  
Sharp Bargains, LLC is committed to protecting your privacy. Our pledge is to safeguard any information we collect associated with you and your business operations.

**Information Collection.**  
We may use third-party advertising companies to help tailor site content to users or to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and web beacons to measure advertising effectiveness (such as which web pages are visited or what products are purchased and in what amount). Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and web beacons is not linked to any personal information collected by us.

**Information Use and Disclosure.**   
Internal Use. We use your personal information to process your order and provide you with customer service. We may internally use your personal information to improve the Sites’ content and layout, to improve outreach and for our own marketing efforts including marketing our services and products to you. In order to facilitate such use and the other use described we may share your information with affiliates under Sharp Bargains, LLC’s control. Only authorized Sharp Bargains, LLC employees will have access to stored information, which we will hold in the strictest confidence.  
Communications with You: We will use your personal information to communicate with you about the site, your orders and deliveries. We may send you a service-related announcement on the rare occasions when it is necessary (for example, if we must temporarily suspend our website for maintenance.) Also, you may submit your email address for reasons such as to receive newsletters. If you submit your email address, we use it to deliver the information to you. We always permit you to unsubscribe or opt out of future emails.

External Use.We want to provide you with outstanding service and to offer you a great selection. We do not sell, rent, trade, license or otherwise disclose your specific personal information or financial information to anyone other than to affiliates under Sharp Bargains, LLC’s control, except that:

As do most catalog and Internet retailers, we sometimes use others to perform specific functions on our behalf. When we disclose information to these service providers, we disclose information to help them to perform their service. For example, in order to deliver products to you, we must share some information. We partner with third parties (such as the U.S. Postal Service, United Parcel Service) to ship products, to ensure delivery, and so that we can obtain feedback, improve the quality of our service, and measure and improve the quality of the service of the third party. In the example of shippers, we provide them some personally identifiable information such as your name, shipping address, email, and phone number.

Similarly, to help you buy products and provide customer service to you, we must provide your credit card number to financial-services corporations such as credit-card processors and issuers. When we submit your credit card number for authorization, we use state-of-the-art data encryption to protect your information. 

We may disclose such information in response to requests from law enforcement officials conducting investigations; subpoenas; a court order; or if we are otherwise required to disclose such information by law. We also will release personal information where disclosure is necessary to protect our legal rights, enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect ourselves or others. For example, we may share information to reduce the risk of fraud or if someone uses or attempts to use the Site for illegal reasons or to commit fraud.

We may share non-personal information (such as the number of daily visitors to a particular web page, or the size of an order placed on a certain date) with third parties such as advertising partners. This information does not directly personally identify you or any user.  
We may publicly disclose the name, city, and state of the contest and sweepstakes winners.

Sharp Bargains, LLC (sharpbargains.com) knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Allscreen Image Marketing, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

The information we learn from Customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Allscreenonline.com. Here are the types of information we gather.

**Information You Give Us**   
We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, and communicating with you.

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission between your browser and our servers. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**   
Our business changes frequently, and our Privacy Notice and the Terms of Use will change also. You should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes; it is your sole responsibility if it changes without notice. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of Customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected Customers.

**Copyright**   
The information and photography contained in this web site are the property of Sharp Bargains, LLC and its affiliates are not to be used, distributed, modified, or reposted without express written authorization from Sharp Bargains, LLC. All contents © 2011 Sharp Bargains, LLC. 

Revised May 6th 2011.
